<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resumecontents on JL-PORTFOLIO</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/resumecontent/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resumecontents on JL-PORTFOLIO</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/resumecontent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Courses</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resumecontent/courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resumecontent/courses/</guid>
      <description>2024 The Odin Project - Foundational Course Extensive course in event-driven programming and front-end software development. Some of the topics included: version control with git, algorithmic understanding, JavaScript, html and css.&#xA;2022 Wwise 301 - Wwise Unity Integration A course which covers the integration between Wwise and Unity and covers all the tools necessary to implement audio and music from Wwise into the Unity game engine.&#xA;Wwise 201 - Interactive Music A course which covers everything related to implementing dynamic music with Wwise and highly focused on the possibilities and obstacles present when composing in an interactive context.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resumecontent/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resumecontent/education/</guid>
      <description>2021 - 2024 Audio Design | Aarhus University Master of Science (MSc) in Information Technology (Digital Design, Audio Design).&#xA;2017 - 2020 Bachelor of Music | The Royal Academy of Music With a focus on audio engineering and production, sound design and contemporary electronic music.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resumecontent/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resumecontent/experience/</guid>
      <description>Jun 2024 - present Frontend Developer Project | Part time Web design and development&#xA;Project Management UX/UI design HTML, CSS, Javascript Versions Control (Git) From design to development of my portfolio website I have gained a lot of knowledge with the general concepts of web frontend development.&#xA;Aug 2023 - Feb 2024 Technical Sound Designer Company: Gumbo Games (startup) | Part time Developing audiosystems in Unity with C#. Using the version control software tool Git in the development process.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
